{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956234451","data":{"timestamp":" 946956234451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956243536","data":{"timestamp":" 946956243536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956245165","data":{"timestamp":" 946956245164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956249145","data":{"timestamp":" 946956249144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956250745","data":{"timestamp":" 946956250745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956253121","data":{"timestamp":" 946956253121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956254749","data":{"timestamp":" 946956254748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956258158","data":{"timestamp":" 946956258158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956259767","data":{"timestamp":" 946956259766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956262426","data":{"timestamp":" 946956262426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956264071","data":{"timestamp":" 946956264071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956271478","data":{"timestamp":" 946956271477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956273088","data":{"timestamp":" 946956273088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956281057","data":{"timestamp":" 946956281057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956282689","data":{"timestamp":" 946956282689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956285241","data":{"timestamp":" 946956285241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956286863","data":{"timestamp":" 946956286863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956289570","data":{"timestamp":" 946956289570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956291191","data":{"timestamp":" 946956291190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956295158","data":{"timestamp":" 946956295157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956296788","data":{"timestamp":" 946956296787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956299214","data":{"timestamp":" 946956299214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956300824","data":{"timestamp":" 946956300823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956303475","data":{"timestamp":" 946956303474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956305070","data":{"timestamp":" 946956305069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956307822","data":{"timestamp":" 946956307821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956309847","data":{"timestamp":" 946956309845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956309984","data":{"timestamp":" 946956309984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 02fb37fc-e0c0-411d-bc6a-9eedc2f81931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956323681","data":{"timestamp":" 946956323679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956329478","data":{"timestamp":" 946956329478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" START_PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956330468","data":{"timestamp":" 946956330467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956331383","data":{"timestamp":" 946956331382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956332133","data":{"timestamp":" 946956332132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956335407","data":{"timestamp":" 946956335407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956337984","data":{"timestamp":" 946956337982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956339611","data":{"timestamp":" 946956339610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956341938","data":{"timestamp":" 946956341937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956343558","data":{"timestamp":" 946956343557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956346115","data":{"timestamp":" 946956346114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956347724","data":{"timestamp":" 946956347723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956352484","data":{"timestamp":" 946956352483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956354072","data":{"timestamp":" 946956354071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956359788","data":{"timestamp":" 946956359788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956361404","data":{"timestamp":" 946956361403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956364105","data":{"timestamp":" 946956364104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956365715","data":{"timestamp":" 946956365714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956368276","data":{"timestamp":" 946956368275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956369884","data":{"timestamp":" 946956369883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956375882","data":{"timestamp":" 946956375881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956377530","data":{"timestamp":" 946956377529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956380139","data":{"timestamp":" 946956380138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956381748","data":{"timestamp":" 946956381747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956384205","data":{"timestamp":" 946956384204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956385818","data":{"timestamp":" 946956385817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956388364","data":{"timestamp":" 946956388364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956390388","data":{"timestamp":" 946956390386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956390466","data":{"timestamp":" 946956390465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062337"," gameId":" 7ac4be5e-5867-43d9-a459-e57e87e7c783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}